recruitmenthunt.com 2017-08-02

# Privacy Policy |

Skip to content

By using recruitmenthunt.com site and its services, you are accepting the Privacy Statement of this website. If you do not agree or in any case of any issues with our web services then you are requested to feel free and share your views with us through our “Contact Us.”

At recruitmenthunt.com the privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. In general, you can visit recruitmenthunt.com without revealing any of your personal information. Our Internet servers may collect the domain names and IP address of our visitor’s device in order to measure the number of visits, average time spent on our website, pages viewed and other similar information. The main intention of recruitmenthunt.com is to improvise and develop the excellent information sources to our visitors.

For our better and extended services to our visitors, we may ask you to provide certain information to us. We are always committed to safeguarding the Personal Information of our users and never share their information with other third parties. Therefore, we have adopted this Privacy Statement in the genuine handling of your personal information.

**Cookies and Web Beacon**

recruitmenthunt.com use cookies to store information about our visitor’s interests and preferences. The third-party ad networks associated with us i.e Google Adsense may use cookies to their advertisement improvements which appear on recruitmenthunt.com Other technologies such as JavaScript, Web Beacons may also be accessed by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness and efficiency of their advertisement links.

**Cookies used by ThirdParties**

recruitmenthunt.com **do not** have any access to the cookies which are used by third-party advertisers. You should check the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more information about the cookies. As some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partner is Google AdSense.

**Copyrights**

If any website wishes to link to our site. It should follow the following guidelines.

  * If you want to access the content from the recruitmenthunt.com then you should give credit to www.recruitmenthunt.com with the hyperlink pointing to our domain name or related web page.
  * Never publish any of the articles from our site without our permission and without giving proper credits to our website.
  * Violations of these rules are strictly prohibited and you have to face the legal issues later.

Finally, we always wish to maintain a cordial relationship with our visitors. So, we are always happy to hear any suggestions, queries from our visitors. Please feel free and contact us at recruitmenthunt.com@gmail.com
